你的巴尼叔叔总是有点神秘
Your Uncle Barney was always always a bit of an enigma.
住在纽约的那些年里
In all the years we lived in New York,
我们当中没有一个人踏进 过他家的门槛
none of us had ever set foot in his apartment.
直到那天 某人甚至出现他的床上
Until one day, one of us did.
这是个有趣的故事
It's a pretty good story.
信不信由你 这一切和酒精都没有关系
And believe it or not, alcohol did not play a role.
所有的一切都开始于两周前 给莉莉的乔迁派对上
It all started two weeks earlier at Lily's housewarming.
两周前
Hey, welcome to my new home.
欢迎光临寒舍
莉莉 这就是
Oh, wow, Lily, this is...
你的新公寓就这样?
Oh, this is all of it.
是的 我知道是小了点 不过这就是特点
Yeah, I know it's small, but it's got character.
谢谢
Thank you.
我最近在跟邻居学立陶宛语
And I am learning Lithuanian from my neighbors.
他们真是太有意思了
They're great.
你也看见了 他们总是在大堂那
They're always out there in the hall, you know,
做饭 打牌 还相互剪头
cooking and gambling and giving each other haircuts.
真有趣
It's nice.
你的厨房和厕所是一起的?
Hey, is that a toilet in your kitchen?
或者说炉子在你浴室?
Or a stove in your bathroom?
这个不是一般的炉子
Oh, that's not just a stove.
这是炉皇(stovenkerator＝ stove+oven+sink+refrigerator)
That's a stovenkerator:
它集火炉 水池 烤箱还有冰箱为一体
a combination of a stove, oven and sink and refrigerator.
炉皇
Stovenkerator.
是不是很酷啊 超现实主义
Isn't that futuristic?
我的神啊 怎么这样
God, I hope not.
墨菲床很酷啊 (墨菲床：一种不用时可折起放进壁橱的床)
Hey, cool Murphy bed.
是啊 有点乱 今早懒得整理了 所以
Yeah, it's kind of a mess. I didn't make my bed this morning, so...
Oh!
你知道吗? 有个新说法
You know what, I bet sleeping at this angle is good for you.
以这个角度入睡对身体有利
For some reason.
我明白了
I got it.
他是说 什么 什么 我就要 什么 什么
That was, something, something, I am going to, something,
你是一个 什么 什么 驴
you like a, something, donkey.
Huh.
多么奇特的文化啊
Other cultures.
不要管他了 我来看看你们送的果篮
Hey, let's break out the fruit basket.
奇怪?有谁吃把它吃了
Hey, who ate all the...?
本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作 仅供学习交流之用 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为 欢迎访问YYeTs美剧论坛进行交流 www YYETS com
老爸老妈的浪漫史 第二季 第五集
翻译：     AYA (小新）    校对：     雨亦奇
后期：     oliver0951      字幕监制：  叶煦
最终我们不得不从莉莉的房间逃离 她有个老鼠室友
Okay, we have to get Lily out of that apartment. Her roommate is a raccoon.
我想让她来我那住 可是我有只狗 她对狗毛过敏
I'd offer her my place, but I've got dogs and she's allergic.
狗?  我跟她前男友住一起 她对那个估计更敏感
Dogs? I live with her ex-boyfriend. I think she's a little more allergic to that.
你那可以吗?巴尼 我知道你那里很神秘
What about your place, Barney? I know it's shrouded in mystery,
但肯定会有个沙发
but it's gotta have a couch.
想住巴尼超人的城堡？没门! (他把fortress of solitude 改称fortress of barnitude  把自己比作超人)
The Fortress of Barnitude? No way.
别这样 她很惨啊
Come on. She's desperate.
我对我要带回去的女人是有条件的
Hmm, normally a prerequisite for the women I bring home,
但是 她不予考虑
but... pass.
你们当中的一个人非常非常走运
One of you guys is very, very lucky because I have...
因为有张多的艾拉妮丝・莫莉塞特演唱会的票 谁想去?
a boom, an extra ticket to the Alanis Morissette concert. Who's in?
- 很明显 没有 - 不
- Absolutely not. - No.
见鬼! 大概一个月前我就搞到票了 当时想和莉莉一起去
Damn! I got these tickets, like, months ago for me and Lily
现在想找个伴都找不到
and now I can't find anyone to go with me.
所以很怀念以前成双入对的日子
This is what I miss about being in a couple.
这样总有人可以陪我去演唱会
I always had someone to go to concerts with,
去菜市场
or farmer's market,
还有早午餐
or brunch.
上帝  我上午没有吃饭
God, I miss brunch!
这样的话我认为你可以自己吃早午餐
Well, I guess you could-- well, you could try going to brunch alone.
你认为我没有试过?
Oh, you don't think I've tried?
一位
Table for one.
一对?
One couple?
不 就我一个人
Um, no, just me.
真的?
Really?
一个人的早午餐?
For brunch?
对 我不是开玩笑
You're right. Who am I kidding?
波普餐厅 真是个好地方 明天我们去吃早午餐吧
Ooh, The Popover Pantry. That place is great. Can we go get brunch tomorrow?
可以啊 亲爱的
Of course, sweetie.
我能跟你们一起去吗?
Can I go with you guys?
确定?跟我们去吃早午饭?
Really? For brunch?
上帝!我讨厌单身!
God, I hate being single!
好吧 我赌匹兹堡赢
Okay, I'll take the over on the Pittsburgh game.
匹兹堡对西雅图　两个星期以来
Oh, and P. to the S., I never got my payout
我就没在西雅图上面赢过钱
from Seattle from two weeks ago.
好的  不要逼我向赌博委员会投诉你
Yeah. Don't make me call the gaming commission on you.
我肯定他们会对这很感兴趣
I'm sure they'd be very interested to know what's going on over there.
好吗?明白吗?
All right? All right?
我也爱你 妈妈 多保重
Okay, I love you, too, Mom. Take care.
莉莉! 你好
Hello,  Lily.
你成功的获取了我的机密
You've somehow managed to circumvent my security.
你怎么做到的
How did you do it?
泰德把备用钥匙给我了
Ted gave me your spare key.
备用钥匙! 太聪明了!
Spare key, brilliant!
我很不好意思 不过我也就只能来这了
I'm sorry, but you know I'd only come here
我没别地儿可去了
if I had no other choice.
今晚  我正准备早点睡觉的时候
But earlier today, I was getting ready to go to sleep and...
你好 （立陶宛语）
Sveikas.
太糟了
That's terrible.
好吧 改天见
Well, see ya.
晕 我今晚不能留下吗?
Well, can I stay here maybe?
我很愿意 但是房间不够
Oh... I'd let you, but I don't have any room.
但是你住的是两室的房间啊
You live in a two-bedroom apartment.
你用一间屋子专门放衣服
You have one room just for your suits.
在我生命里 我的衣服也是家庭成员
Hey, I'm at a point in my life where my suits are my family.
莉莉 看看周围
Look around you, Lily.
你现在置身于 一个单身汉的国度
You are in the heart of bachelor country,
作为一个女人 你在我这里是不受欢迎的
and as a woman, you are an illegal immigrant here.
现在你可以申请一张只有 12小时的"性"签证
Now, you can try to apply for a sex visa, but that only lasts 12 hours.
如果你床上功夫好的话 还有长达14小时的多次往返签证
14 if you qualify for multiple entry.
要是单纯的小女生肯定说 "不会吧"
Eww... is something some lame, judgmental chick would say,
但是我要得到多次往返签证 来　击掌
but I say give me multiple high fives.
哇　你真是不顾一切
Wow, you really are desperate.
那确实
I really am.
好吧 你可以待两天
Okay, you can stay here for two days.
只有一条你要遵守 不能乱动我的东西
But I only have one rule. You can't change anything.
我没有理由乱动你的东西 这里真是...
Why would I change anything? This place is...
...完美
...perfect.
除了你没有电视这个事实
Except for the fact that you don't have a TV.
看见那面墙了吗?
See that wall?
300寸的液晶电视
300-inch flat-screen.
只有东京有卖的 但是我有个熟人
They only sell them in Japan, but I know a guy.
用了一艘可以装下金刚的船 才把它弄回来的
Had to ship it over in a tugboat like freakin' King Kong.
亮的晃眼睛
It hurts my eyes.
是啊 这光无法关掉
Yeah. That doesn't go away.
- 嘿 - 嘿 你去哪了?
- Hey. - Hey, where have you been?
艾拉妮丝・莫莉塞特的演唱会
The Alanis Morissette concert.
一个人?
By yourself?
事实上我是和一个法学院的朋友去的
No, actually I went with a friend from law school.
真的?她是谁啊?
Oh, really? Who's this friend?
布莱德
Brad.
- 兄弟  艾拉妮丝・莫莉塞特摇滚? - 完全正确
- Bro, Alanis Morissette rocks! - Totally!
不可思议吧 我今晚差点就不能来了
I can't believe I almost didn't come tonight.
我猜  这两张票是你打算和莉莉一起去的
Let me guess: You bought the tickets for you and Lily
在她甩了你之前
right before she dumped you.
是啊 你怎么知道的
Yeah, how'd you know?
我也才被甩了
I just got dumped myself.
什么?卡洛跟你分手了?
What, Kara broke up with you?
很遗憾 这太郁闷了
I'm sorry, man. That sucks.
布莱德你喜欢早午饭吗?
Brad, do you like brunch?
你请他吃早午饭?
You invited him to brunch?
是啊 我请了 有问题?
Yeah, I invited him to brunch. Why, is that weird?
是的 问题就在于 你邀请他一起吃早午饭
Yes. That's why I was all, "You invited him to brunch?"
为什么朋友就不能去吃呢?
Why can't two guys who are friends go to brunch?
因为这个有点
Because brunch is kind of...
娘娘腔
G irly.
娘娘腔?早餐不娘娘腔
Girly? Breakfast isn't girly.
午饭不娘娘腔 偏偏早午餐有?
Lunch isn't girly. What makes brunch girly?
我不知道
I don't know.
比如说马听起来娘娘腔
There's nothing girly about a horse.
角也没有
Nothing girly about a horn,
但是独角兽听说来就娘娘腔
but put them together and you get a unicorn.
管你们怎么说
I don't care what either of you say,
我要和布莱德去波普餐厅
I am going to The Popover Pantry with Brad.
我们去了 我们饿了
We're here. We're hungry.
习惯早午餐吧
Get used to it, brunch.
-闻起来真香 - 谢谢夸奖
- Hmm... smells delicious. - Thank you.
冰箱里没有吃的了 所以我买了点
There was no food in the fridge, so I picked up...
你在做什么?
What are you doing?
莉莉 再重复一遍规矩
Lily, what was the first rule again?
不要乱动任何东西!
Don't change anything.
那第二条是什么?
And what was the second rule?
-规则二 没有规则二? - 是的!
- There was no second rule. - Exactly!
这里只有一条规则 而你破了规矩
There was only one rule and you broke it.
我买食物 这个也算?
I bought groceries. That counts as changing something?
莉莉 如果我想要冰箱 里放满了食物
Lily, if I wanted a fridge full of groceries,
或者早上有新鲜的咖啡
or fresh coffee in the morning,
那我早就去找女朋友了
I'd be in a relationship.
但是!我不想有女朋友
But I don't want to be in a relationship.
这就是为什么我明确的告诉 每一个来这里的女孩
That's why I make it crystal-clear to every girl that walks through that door
这里不是放牙刷的地方
that this is not a place to leave a toothbrush.
也不是放隐形眼镜盒的地方
This  is not a place to leave a contact lens case.
此地不宜久留
This is a place to leave.
来 我带你去看看
Come on, I'll give you a tour.
禁止照相
Uh, no flash photography, please.
欢迎来到卧室
Bienvenido to the bedroom.
看 超大的床
Dig this: king-sized bed,
大毛毯 一个枕头
full-sized blanket, one pillow.
这些东西都在对曾睡过的人说 这没你的事了　你可以走了
Everything about this bed says, "our work here is done."
接下来是盥洗室
Next we say "bienvenue" to the bathroom.
为什么只有一条毛巾?
What, only one towel?
为什么没有电吹风?
What, no hairdryer?
你知道我把东西都放哪吗? 你住的房间 想多了
You know where I keep that stuff? Your place. Beat it.
接下来看最优雅
And the coup de grace...
看见了吧
Yeah, that's right.
这个还没有申请专利
Patent-pending.
这里是通向客厅的走廊
And wilkommen to the hallway.
当像泰德还有马修还要 把A片藏起的时候
While guys like Ted and Marshall may hide their porn...
马修 他没有A片
Marshall doesn't have porn.
真有趣
Aww, that's sweet.
当像泰德还有马修还要 把A片藏起的时候
While guys like Ted and Marshall may hide their porn,
我把我的A片  展示出来
I had mine... professionally lit.
当那些女的看见这些的时候 只恨自己不能飞过去
Girls see this, they can't get out of here fast enough.
如果这些还赶不走他们的话
And if that doesn't drive them away,
还有你的克隆人战士模型
there's always your life-sized storm-trooper.
那不是用来吓人的 个人收藏
No, that's just awesome.
正如你看见的 只要是女的在我这醒来
So you see, whenever a girl wakes up here,
我从来都不用告诉她另筑爱巢
I never have to tell her to go build her nest somewhere else.
我的公寓已经告诉她了
My apartment does it for me.
天啊 我最爱早午饭
God, I love brunch.
爽啊
Oh, damn...
这个南瓜真是太太太好吃了
the zucchini bread is "ridonculous."
两个男人吃饭并不古怪　对吧?
This isn't weird, right?
我曾这么想过
I sort of thought it might be,
但现在却不这么认为
but it totally isn't.
顺便问下 你没有怂恿巴尼?
And B-T-dub, you totally did not oversell the eggs Benny.
是的? 有问题?
Right? Right?
我是说 为什么我们两个难兄难弟
I mean, why can't two single bros
就不能想象今天一样去听摇滚
go out and rock brunch Sunday morning-style?
确实是 谢谢 这正是我想要说的
Exactly. Thank you, that's exactly what I've been saying.
这就是命运
This must be destiny.
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
我有两张周五晚上的 Mamma Mia (ABBA的歌曲) 的演出票
I have two tickets for Mamma Mia Friday night.
你喜欢阿巴 是吗? （ABBA是一支瑞典的流行乐乐队）
You like Abba, right?
我在说什么? 谁不是这样?
What am I saying? Who doesn't?
不管怎么说 本来是要和卡洛一起去的 现在就剩你我
Anyway, I was gonna take Kara, but now it's all you and me.
我们两个大男人去百老汇 你认为怎么样？
We're gonna do Broadway, bro style. What do you say?
好!
Yeah!
你被冻醒了?
Hey. Did the cold wake you?
没有 我一直在看你睡觉
No, I've just been watching you sleep.
你想洗澡吗? 但是我只有一条毛巾
Oh, did you try and take a shower? I'm sorry, I only have one clean towel.
我从不买要天天洗澡这理论的帐
I don't buy into the myth that we need to shower every day.
好吧
Okay.
你想喝咖啡吗? 但是我这里没有了 想喝的话你得出去自己买
I'd offer you some coffee, but I don't have any, so you're gonna have to...
我抵制咖啡
I'm boycotting coffee.
但你不妨喝喝那些哥伦比亚农民的血汗
You may as well drink the tears of a Colombian peasant farmer.
上帝啊 我喜欢这里
God, I love this place.
还有个好消息 我没有工作
Good thing I don't have a job
所以我可以整天整天的待在这里
because I could stay here all day.
我想我有什么东西忘在书架上了
I think I left something on the bookshelf.
不要 看这些
Whoops. Oh, no, oh, look.
我太低级趣味了
Oh, I'm disgusting.
你从不隐瞒自己的欲望
Wow, you're open about your sexuality
这也是我爱你的一个原因
and that's one of the reasons I love you.
我说我爱你了吗?
Did I just say that?
好吧 我向你表白吧
Oh, well, cat's out of the bag.
我爱你
I love you.
援兵　援兵　快来吧
Whoa, uh... Okay, beep, beep. Backing up, um...
巴尼
Hi, Barney. Oh...
哦 上帝啊 你结婚了? 这个是你老婆
Oh, my God. Are you married? Is this your wife?
什么?不
What? No.
对!
Yes!
- 真的? - 真的!
- Yes? - Yes.
狗娘养的!
You son of a bitch!
难以置信 你亵渎了我心里最神圣的东西
I can't believe I let you enter my sacred temple.
嘿 别这样好不好 亲爱的 听我解释
Come on, baby. Please, no. Oh, you don't understand.
我作了什么? 太糟糕了 你怎么能   ?
What have I done? This is the worst. How could you...?
你以后就住这吧
You're not going anywhere.
终于落幕了
Wow, that was close.
那个另类女人都不打算走了
That hippie chick wouldn't leave.
她都准备住着了
She was ready to squat here.
莫非她愿意忍受你的 弹簧座便器?
Well, she'd have to with your spring-loaded toilet seat, wouldn't she?
她对我所在公寓里 做的一切都免疫
She was freakishly immune to everything in my apartment...
除了你
except you.
你甚至好过那些A片
You're  better than porn.
多谢夸奖
Thank you.
你想继续住在我这吗?
How would you like to extend your stay here?
你所做的只是 假装你是我妻子
All you'd have to do is pretend to be my wife,
吓走我的那些一夜情
and scare off the occasional one-night stand.
我知道 我知道 你有你的道德底线还有原则
I know, I know. You've got your ethics. You've got your principles...
好啊 我愿意
I'll do it.
真的?
Really?
巴尼 你的母亲的诸多问题让你
Barney, you've clearly got some serious mother issues
感情空虚的如同一只耗子
that have left you the emotional equivalent of a scavenging sewer rat.
但是 在我的公寓里 我要...
But, in my other apartment, I would be living
一只真正的耗子生活 所以我留下
with an actual scavenging sewer rat, so you win.
我接受
I'll take it.
- Mamma Mia? - Mamma Mia?
- Mamma Mia? - Mamma Mia.
你知道什么 这个可是个经典歌舞剧
You know what? It's supposed to be a great musical, okay?
他赢了托尼奖的所有奖项
It won all sorts of Tonys and stuff.
总之这听起来就象 令人激动 第三次约会
No, totally. It sounds like a really, really fun, exciting, third date.
第三次约会 你知道这个意味着什么吗?(Robin在模仿啪啪时候床的吱吱声)
Ooh, third date. You know what that means.
老大们 服你了 这个不是约会
It is not a date, okay.
兄弟两个去看百老汇有问题?
It's just two bros taking in a Broadway show.
你们两个在看表演之前 吃饭吗?
You bros going to get dinner beforehand?
说不定我们去吃点牛排
We might grab a steak, yeah.
在那吃?
Where at?
爱情咖啡馆
Cafe L'Amour.
布莱德说那的东西好吃! 好不好
Brad says the food is really good there, okay.
听起来 布莱德安排好了一切了
Sounds like Brad's got quite the night planned out.
你最好准备个A计划
You better bring your "A" game.
穿性感内裤
That means no granny panties.
好吧 你们知道吗 你们俩感到有危险
All right, you know what? You two are just threatened
就是因为我是个出现 在你们当中的灯泡?
because I'm a single guy moving in on your couples' turf.
好吧 告诉你们 这是我自己的事情
Well, guess what? It's my territory now.
我在早午饭已经计划好了 丰盛的晚餐 还有 精彩的音乐剧
I'm peeing all over brunches, fancy dinners and musicals.
没错 我和布莱德不去百老汇了
That's  right; Brad and I are taking back Broadway.
你打算穿什么?
What are you going to wear?
我是这样打算的 有领的T恤还有条纹西装
I was thinking like this collared shirt and these pin...
你知道什么 闭嘴
Oh, you know what? Shut up.
能把报纸的娱乐版递给我吗?
Can you pass the Arts and Leisure?
我才递给你的?
I just did.
亲爱的 我
Honey, I'm...
巴尼 这发生什么?
Barney, what the hell is going on here?
莉莉 听我解释
Lily, I can explain...
你怎么 在家里!
How could you? In our own home?
你这杂种!
You bastard!
- 对不起 我不知道他 - 滚出去
- I'm so sorry. I didn't know he had... - Just get out.
这就是我为了这个家庭 跳了四年脱衣舞
This is what I get after I worked as a stripper for four years
让你去上医学院所得的回报
to put you through medical school?
我还为你隆胸
I got breast implants for you.
我   我还准备掉几滴眼泪呢
I... I was just about to turn on the tears.
你演得太精彩了
Brava.
简直难以置信
That was incredible.
而且那记耳光也是如假包换 你一点也没留情
And that slap was genius. You did not hold back.
是 那是我一直想做的
Yeah, that I just always wanted to do.
那我们都扯平了
Fair enough.
我不得不说
I have to say,
有时候在这里吃东西感觉不错
it's kind of nice having food around here for a change.
你知道
You know...
算了
nah, never mind.
说吧 什么?
What?
你是我妻子 你不用顾忌什么
You're my wife. You can tell me anything.
如果你真的希望 别人都上你的当的话
Well, if you really wanted to sell this ruse,
你应该试图把这里变得...
we should try to make this place a little more...
你知道 家的感觉
you know, homey.
就像是真的有个女人住这
Like-like a woman would actually live here.
你怎么打算?
What did you have in mind?
# Bones, bones, brittle little bones #
# It's not the milk you seek #
# It's the sun you need #
# Sugar dumpling, muffin baby #
# This world is going crazy #
# Do do do do #
# Do do do do do #
你回来了啊
Hey, you're home.
我们以为你要明早才回来
I didn't think we'd be seeing you until tomorrow morning.
哈哈 这又不是约会
Ha, ha, ha, ha. It wasn't a date.
即使是约会 也是个奇怪的约会
Okay, it was a date and it got way weird.
你不用这么客气
Oh, you really don't have to do that.
不 这次我请 你是我的客人
No, I insist. You're my guest.
谢谢你 布莱德
Thanks, Brad.
兄弟
Bro,
巧克力吃到你脸上了
you got some chocolate on your chin.
没擦掉
Still there.
我来吧 傻男孩
I'll get that bad boy.
哇～
Whoa.
这还会更糟
Well, it could have been worse.
难说弄到你嘴里了
It  could have fallen in your lap.
越来越糟
It gets worse.
不 不用 我可以自己搞定 谢谢 布莱德
No, I-I can do it, Brad. Okay, thank you.
不管怎么样 这个周六...
So anyway, ah, it's this Saturday.
你想来嘛?
Do you want to come?
你想让我和你一起去参加婚礼?
You want me to go to a wedding with you?
还好啊 不是太糟
Okay, that's not too bad.
两个单身男人在婚礼上四处游荡 有点不速之客的感觉
Two single guys on the prowl. It'll be like Wedding Crashers.
不要让布莱德接到花束就好
Just keep Brad away from the bouquet.
比这还要糟
It gets worse.
看起来好多了
It gets better.
这时候的佛蒙特州风景特别好
The foliage in Vermont this time of year is ridonc.
佛蒙特州?
Vermont?
是啊 婚礼在一家B&B(床和早餐)饭店举行
Yeah, the wedding's at this awesome B&B.
卡莱和我以前经常去那
Kara and I used to go there.
不管怎么说我弄到最后一间屋子
Anyway, there is one room left, and we got it.
是不是有点惠特曼的风格 (此人是个双性恋)
Walt Whitman Suite, bro.
你拒绝了 是吗?
You said no, right?
当然
Of course.
我知道
I understand.
是有点酷
It's cool.
这是自从卡莱离开之后
It's the first time I was going to see my college friends
我第一次去见我大学同学
since Kara left me.
我只是
I just...
太想她了
I just miss her so much.
我和你去吧
I'll go to Vermont with you.
太好了!
That's great!
你知道吗? 他们已经在陶吧注册了
You know, uh, they're registered at Pottery Barn.
我们俩可以手把手的做个陶罐
I figure we could go halfsies on a gravy boat.
对不起 现在就不再好笑了
I'm sorry. It's not funny anymore.
都是早午餐惹得祸!
Damn you, brunch!
这家伙疯了 是吗?
This guy's crazy, right?
我不认为他疯了
Look, I don't think he's crazy.
我只是认为他倍受失恋的打击
I just think he's suffering from a severe case of girlfriend withdrawal.
不幸的是 你成为他的精神寄托了
And unfortunately, you're his nicotine patch.
在这段畸形爱恋里 你现在唯一能做的就是
And now you have to do what every dysfunctional couple has to do:
分手
break up.
你们是对的 太对了 但是我答应他
You're right. You're right. I promised Brad
我会陪他一起去的 就这么定了
I would go to the wedding with him, and then that is it.
大好人
Good man.
我认为我们的决定是正确的
Oh, I think we made the right decision
意大利的全棉床上用品
going for the custom-made Italian sheets.
要是我的床也能穿西装的话 那就好了
Hey, if my bed's going suit up, it's going to do it right.
不想出去走走?
Want to give it a whirl?
好吧 我要出去了 去酒吧转转
All right, I'm going to head out, hit the bars.
你今晚做什么?
What are you going to do tonight?
我本来想看电视剧的 但是 上帝啊 你的床太舒服了
Oh, I was just going to watch Letterman but, God this bed is so comfy.
你要是在卧室有个电视就好了
I wish you had a TV in here.
说正经的  你的钱怎么来的啊
Okay, seriously, what do you do for a living?
无可奉告
Please.
我以为你要出去了
I thought you were going out.
恩
Eh.
这段独白之后
After the monologue.
第二天早晨 当阳光开始亲吻曼哈顿时
The next morning, as the sun rose over Manhattan,
你马修叔叔直奔布莱德的公寓去
your Uncle Marshall headed over to Brad's apartment
为了参加在佛蒙特州举行的婚礼
to leave for the wedding in Vermont.
但是 当他到那的时候
But when he got there...
不
No.
不要
No...
不
No.
天啊!
No!
怎么会这样
No.
泰德
Ted.
布莱德为我准备了一束花
Um, Brad got me flowers.
等等
Hold on.
布莱德为他准备了一束花
Brad got him flowers.
不好意思 怎么这么搞笑啊
I'm sorry. It just got funny again.
- 嘿 - 等等 你先听我说
- Oh, hey... - No, Brad, uh, I don't want to hear it.
我是跟你关系不错 海芋百合也是我最喜欢的花
I do like you. And calla lilies are my favorite flower.
我不知道你是怎么知道的 我猜你了解我
I don't know how you knew that. I guess you just get me,
这样并不酷 我简直不能相信你
but this is not cool, man. I can't believe that you would...
- 甜心
- Hey, sweetie. - Hey.
- 马修 你好啊 - 你好 卡莱
- Hey, Marshall. - Hi, Kara.
这样   你们 看上去破镜重圆了?
So you guys, are like, back together now?
是啊 就在昨晚
Yeah. Happened last night.
不好意思 兄弟
Uh, I'm sorry, bro.
- 我应该打电话告诉你的 - 是的 你该打电话告诉我
- I should have called you. - Yeah, you should have.
- 我不是有意的 - 没事  布莱德
- Well, I didn't mean to hurt... - Don't, Brad.
不需要
Just don't.
# There was something # # in the air that night #
# The stars went bright #
他怎么了?
Oh, what was with him?
不知道
I don't know.
我想他爱上我了
I think he's in love with me.
# Fernando #
简直难以致信 我和你
I can't believe we just... you and I...
- 我们都作什么了? - 没什么
- what have we done? - Nothing.
什么都没有发生 我们只是睡着了
Nothing happened. We-we just went to sleep.
仅仅睡着了? 我从来都不睡在这样的床上 一个女士床
Just went to sleep? I don't sleep in the same bed as a woman
更不可能在睡觉的时候不动
and not make a move.
这怎么可能  你...
How could... You.
你肯定非礼了我
You spooned me against my will.
但一个巴掌拍不响的
Hey, it takes two to cuddle.
我们
We...
我们重新布置了我的房子
We redecorated my place.
我们周五晚上在一起看电视
We stayed in on a Friday night to watch Letterman,
睡在一起 居然没有发生性关系
and then slept together and didn't have sex?
我的上帝啊 我们是恋爱关系
Oh, my God, we're in a relationship.
这就是你所谓的恋爱关系?
That's what you think a relationship is?
我原本以为你有免疫力
You were supposed to be the vaccine,
但是你把爱情病传染给了我 你必须得走了
but you gave me the disease. You gotta go.
巴尼
Barney.
我不认为是在对我生气 你是在对自己生气
I don't think you're mad at me. You're mad at yourself.
你放下戒备 让别人能进入你的生活
You let down your guard, and let someone into your life,
事实上这种感觉会很好
and-and it actually felt okay.
但却吓到了你
And that terrifies you.
你得走
Uh-huh. You gotta go.
你怎么能叫我扫地出门? 我在这可是花了不少精力
Hey, you can't just kick me out! I put a lot of work into this place,
还有我开始习惯这种生活
and I've grown accustomed to a certain standard of living.
这种生活? 你什么都没有付出!
A certain standard of living? You didn't pay a single...
就这样在两周的婚姻生活后
And so Mr. and Mrs. Stinson, after two weeks of marriage,
史蒂森夫妇 决定叫停
decided to call it quits.
幸运的是他们达成了个协议
Fortunately, they reached a settlement.
这就是你的关于你的莉莉婶婶 如何装饰她公寓的故事
And that's the story of how Aunt Lily furnished her apartment.
几天之后马修又遇见了布莱德
Marshall ran into Brad again some time later.
上帝啊 布莱德
Oh, my God, it's Brad.
快笑 就当我说了什么笑话
Laugh like I said something really funny.
是吗 是吗
Right, right.
你好 马修
Hey, Marshall.
好 最近怎么样啊?
Oh, hey, hey, how's it going?
不错
It's good.
- 你好 我是 - 你好 我知道你是谁
- Hey, I'm, uh... - Yeah, I know who you are.
好吧 我得走了 我有些事要办
Well, I got to go. I got this thing.
我也有重要的事要办
Yeah, me too, but more important.
那么我们改天见啦
So, I guess I'll see you around.
好啊 好啊
Sure. Sure.
即使你没觉得 你也要跟我说 他变胖了
Even if you don't believe it, tell me he looks fat.
一点不假 是变胖了
Totally looks fat.